I'ma always choose the 500,000, fuck dinner with a beer in there when children don't get dinner right now
Yeah, it's true you sold out, built off the fiends and dope house, black capitalism ain't shit if it means black families getting tore down
You ain't no Fred Hampton nigga, you just a Booker T nigga, watch when you ain't used to white folks hang your teeth nigga
You cut the locks in life Samson, you lost your energy nigga, we been boycotting for years so what the fuck you mean nigga
How you speaking ill on a black man that seen the tragedies of how we bleed and couldn't stand and took a knee
Your moor's been in question ever since you hit the streets but now your soul get in question ever since you hit a B
You ain't a G, keep it a B, Jay, you over your head, lead the politics to B, Jay
You the white man's bitch, your only job's to suck nigga for peep's sake
We shopping cause of monopolies, you in the bed with them probably giving BJ's, what I mean J's, you suck nigga
I only give a fuck nigga, you wanna dance with the devils for some bucks nigga, good luck nigga
We eat the rich, just remember that you stuck with them, the fuck is up with them, I'm really confused
We listen to a dude that made black artists get screwed, the NFL getting rich, our black people on the field getting bruised
These corporations anti-black and he do deals with them too, who the target be
Don't start it G, if we revolted, the only target is your arteries, hit you where your heart would be
No billionaire should be alive, that goes for you and every star you breed
Preaching black excellence while doing business with the devil's men
Laughing courtside when an abuser, enough evidence
Actions ain't been reasonable, I doubt the message settles in
You ain't a revolutionary, you a hurting dog on the settlement
We gotta start to question what a legend is
Is a legend gonna sell out, is a legend gonna dodge accountability and flail out
Is a legend gonna profit off an anti-black bell house
Is a legend gonna talk down, flex on all the people that he quote unquote want help out
Is a legend gonna be silent when there's 17 lynches
Is a legend gonna be fighting to keep blood, money, pension
I wanna see you sentenced
Beyonce was a teen when you started showing interest
I know the skeletons in that closet that you don't wanna mention
Keep tap dancing for them niggas
Keep tap dancing for them fucking niggas
Keep tap dancing for them, Andrew
I'm an engineer, Andrew
awarding the community
And I just want to know that
And I hope you're taking off this
If you don't want to mention this
When your sisterluk has one who can't do that
If you don't want to see you
Like her impact it
We don't want to see you
Like her back out
And we're waiting for us
Okay, no more
Be PSC
Plan
Like her box
You know
Like her life
Bye